Hey Flower, come check this out!
Whatever it is, I don't care!
But Flower, this time it's really important!
Unless it is Dream Island, I don't wanna hear it.
Oh, well... it's a bug.
GAH! HEUGH-EGH!
- AAAHAAA!
- AGH! AAAH!
Oh, my gosh, Firey, I'll save you!
FIREY:
AAA-
-AAAUGH...UUAAAGH!!
HUUH?
BUHHH!
♪ [INTRO PLAYS] ♪
Subtitles: Daniel Adam Valle
So what do we do without the speaky box?
I don't know.
I think it means we all win Dream Island!
No! I think it means I win Dream Island!
I think it means we should use
the replacement box that I built last night.
Yeah, Firey's definitely right!
Bleh!
Rocky!
My replacement box is so much better!
PBBBT!
Hurtful!
That means we're using mine!
Yeah!
- But-but... but! B-b-but-but!
- Wh-wh-hhh-hu-what? But...!
How about we use both?
WE CAN'T USE BOTH!
Why not?
Fine.
Then let's do Cake at Stake!
♪ The points are gone ♪
♪ We are free of them now, but we look on ♪
♪ ♪
♪ To the moment that we see: ♪
♪ The next slice of cake ♪
♪ A step closer to the prize ♪
♪ Brought on by Cake at Stake! ♪
♪ ♪
We got 844 votes, which is fewer than last time!
Oh, that's too bad.
The person who got the
most votes will be eliminated.
I hope that's you!
What? I can't be eliminated; I'm the host.
No, I'm the host!
HAAEEUGH!
Oh, no!
The cake is some Yoylecake!
Oh, they're so cute!
Grr!
Whoa!
I'll give you cake if you're safe.
- Spongy, you had immunity,
- Huh?
so you're safe.
Firey, since you are so amazing and
awesome, you only got sixty-four votes.
Whoa! What's with the tub? And where's the TV?
We had to sell the TV because of budget cuts.
Hmm. It doesn't sound the same when you say that.
Uh, hello? Where's my cake?
Here's your cake!
Hey! Why'd you cut me such a small slice?
Because I hate you! Oh, and I poisoned your cake, too.
Oh, wha?
Leafy, since you are also awesome,
you only got sixty-nine votes.
Yoylecake! And thanks for calling me awesome.
You're welcome.
Oh, no! I think I'm gonna be eliminated!
Well, I sure WISH that were the case, but it's NOT!
Metal Ball, with eighty votes...
...you're safe.
YOYLECAKE!
And it's down to Flower and Rocky.
Personally, I'd be fine with either leaving.
Grr!
Well anyway, let's show the votes.
Wow! It's so close, I can't tell.
And in the closest voting EVER,
Flower manages to stay in the game!
No, she doesn't.
Yeah, she does!
And how did you know?
I just do!
Well, why don't we measure it to find out?
FINE, LET'S!
♪ [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC] ♪
And Rocky is eliminated!
Yes! High five, Leafy!
Uhh, no, thanks.
Finally! No more vomit.
Firey, that wasn't very nice!
Hey Leafy, we made it to the final five!
We are amazing!
We deserve a reward!
Hey, Speakers, can I have a reward?
- You sure can!
- You sure can't!
Ooh, wow! What is it?
It's a house.
Wow! Does it mean we all get houses?
- Yes.
- Yay!
Mine's too small. I want a bigger one!
Well, mine's just the right size!
Hehehe!
WHUH-OH! Whoa!
WAH! WAAAH!
Don't worry, Spongy! We've got backups.
Really?
Stop being so generous!
And besides, we have to get to the CONTEST!
The twenty-second contest is
- a beauty contest! What?! No, it's not!
- To escape a volcano! What?! No, it's not!
Fine. Let's have a vote.
Who wants to escape the volcano?
And who wants a beauty contest?
Mine overrules all of yours!
That means we're going to escape the volcano.
YEAH!
- FLOWER SPEAKER BOX: Ready to go?
- Uh, not quite! I can't find the parachutes!
FLOWER SPEAKER BOX:
Ha-ha! There are no parachutes!
AAAAAH!
The first person to get out of
the volcano wins immunity.
- If you fall into lava-
- Magma.
MAGMA, and DIE,
you have to start all over again!
Oh, my gosh, that's so unfair!
GO!
Huh! Ha-ha!
Hup!
AAAAAAAAH!
HEEUUGH!
Hey! I'm a bubble again.
Yeah!
Heuuugh-HOHOOOH!
Ooh, ooh, ow! Hot!
Oh, I know you can do it,
Flower! Just give it a try!
Heugh-ugh!
AAAAAH!!!
Hey! Why don't we run across
Spongy as he's falling in?
Okay!
BUUUUH!
Yeaaah!
Hup! Hup! Hup! Hup! Hup! Hup!
Whoa-wee!
AAAHH!
BUUUH!
Heh! Heh! Hup! Buah!
Ha-ha! I'm gonna beat you! I'm gonna beat all of you!
And I'm-I'm gonna go on and win Dream Island!
And-and, you're not! Y-you're gonna
get the opposite of Dream Island!
Uh, dr-dream, n-nightmare... Nightmare Moon!
AAAAAH!
Woah! What's going on?
The volcano's erupting!
Oh, no!
Wheeh-whoa!
AHHHH!
AAAAAAAAAAH!
You all escaped the volcano at the
same time, so we need a tie-breaker.
- And what is the tie-breaker-
- A BEAUTY CONTEST!
- We're both judges!
- Okay!
I think Flower's the most beautiful!
Well, I think Firey has the most beauty.
I guess they both get immunity then!
- YAY!
- YEAH!
FIREY SPEAKER BOX:
Bubble, Leafy, and Spongy are up for elimination.
Vote one of them right now! Whoever gets
the most votes WILL BE ELIMINATED!